Hamamatsu, home of yummy eel...
Fujinomiya, land of tasty shigure...
I must have come pretty far up.
What a nice view.
I might spoil the view from the
campsite if I enjoy it now!
I see nothing.
Do I go straight from here?
This area's looking more forested.
It must be scary walking here at night.
Hello!
Hello.
Fujikawa Healthy
Greenspace Campsite
I made it to the campsite!
(2) Episode 8
Camping Alone
It's so open!
I can still see Mt. Fuji, too!
The washroom's so clean.
This is the cooking pavilion.
I'm not allowed to make a
fire outside of here, right?
I can't have a campfire, but it's not
too cold, so I guess it's all right.
I could camp in the rain!
I can't connect to the internet...
Hello!
Hello.
It's a relief to know there
are other campers around.
This view must be really nice at night.
You can see all the way to Izu.
Well...
Time to start solo camping!
Home of yummy eel...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Oh, I think I can fix it.
Tent's all set!
It's a lot of work doing it alone.
Now...
Rin-chan said solo camping is boring
if you don't have anything to do.
For me, it's gotta be...
this!
Shimeji
Salmon Fillets
Tokaido Butter
Outdoor cooking research!
Aluminum Foil
If it's good, I can share it with the
others when we go camping together.
As long as I'm cooking for myself,
it's no bother to anyone if I mess up.
What are you doing, Onee-chan?
That girl's camping on her own.
Maybe she's a loner.
A loner?
No...
Max Height 3.4 m
Max Width 3.5 m
Closed for winter
Not again...
Just kidding.
I read about this yesterday.
This tunnel leads to Yashajin Pass, doesn't it?
So creepy.
I would've been really
let down if I hadn't known,
but there's something awe-inspiring
about seeing it like this.
I guess it's that wabi-sabi aesthetic.
Hayakawa
I still love quiet lakes.
I think the campsite is around there,
and that road leads to Shizuoka.
Rindou Ikawa Amehata Line
The Rindou Ikawa Amehata Line
is the only route
that takes you from Yamanashi
to Lake Ikawa in Shizuoka.
The road's under repair
right now after falling apart.
Caution
I want to try taking it once it's open again.
A suspension bridge...
It's sturdier than I thought.
The middle part rocks!
Wait, the trail past the
bridge looks even worse...
I should go back and hit the hot spring.
Deer.
Bear.
Boar.
I've heard deer isn't too gamey...
Actually, isn't the braised bear paw in
high-end Chinese restaurants game, too?
Search
braised bear paw recipe
Is it even something you can prepare at home?
Braised
Bear
Paw
Braised bear paw.
First, stew the bear paw with ginger
and green onion for four or five hours
to get rid of the smell.
After that, use tweezers to remove all hairs.
Once that's done, stew it for
another four hours or so until tender.
Remove the outer skin, bone, and claws.
That completes the preparations.
We're now ready to start cooking.
Hello.
I'd like some of this deer meat.
Welcome!
Welcome
Hot springs are the best when
they're on the particularly hot side.
There's a cafeteria here.
Maybe I'll go to the campsite
after I'm done eating.
I should send a photo of Lake Amehata.
Come to think of it,
Nadeshiko's stopped sending me photos.
She hasn't read my messages, either.
I wonder why...
Nadeshiko
Calling
The customer you have dialed
has switched off their phone
or is out of the service area.
It's up in the mountains over there.
She must be out of range.
Probably.
Nadeshiko is just out of range.
Nadeshiko is just out of range...
Is she really?
Darn it!
It's going to bug me.
I'm the reason she decided
to go camping on her own.
I'm sure I'm just being a worrywart, but...
I'm gonna go shopping and then head to the campsite!
Fujikawa Healthy Greenspace Campsite
Should we have dinner?
Okay.
Are you sure you two are happy with
convenience store meals for a camping trip?
Yeah.
We all like different things, anyway.
It's a lot of work for you to cook, isn't it?
I wouldn't have minded cooking for once.
This is better than the food he does cook.
I know.
I heard that.
Okay, we'll go warm up yours, too.
Okay.
Be careful.
Onee-chan, what is that girl doing?
An unholy ritual?
Tonight's dinner is whole
veggies roasted in foil.
Outdoor Cooking
Experiments
Whole veggies
roasted in foil
First, give the veggies a quick rinse.
Root veggies should be wrapped in
wet newspaper and aluminum foil.
Other veggies should be wrapped
in foil and tossed into the fire.
Hot!
Hot
Then you wait.
Use smaller, thinner root vegetables
to ensure that they cook evenly.
Sweet Potato: 30 mins
Different veggies require
different cooking times.
Carrot: 30 mins
Tomato: 10 mins
Eggplant: 10 mins
Potato: 30 mins
Gummies: 5 secs
Avocado: 10 mins
Garlic: 5 mins
Beep Beep Beep
Shazam!
Retrieve the items before they burn,
then season them lightly...
Herb salt
Olive oil
Roasted Tomato
And you're done.
She's cooking in foil!
Yum!
There's nowhere else we can use a stove...
I feel awkward about going in.
What should we do?
Huh?!
Onee-chan, roasted tomato is super good!
When did you get over there?!
What's this?
Potato.
And this one?
Um...
I think that was a carrot.
Hey, have some restraint.
Why, though?
It's all right.
Would you like some, miss?
I have baked apples, too.
She's a witch.
So you're camping with your dad, huh?
Yeah.
Mom's out traveling with her friends.
She said it's a housewives' retreat.
Are you having fun camping?
I dunno.
All we've done is eat snacks and watch anime.
I see.
The next one's done!
What's that?
Whole roasted eggplant.
Help yourselves.
Yum!
You should have some, too.
Okay...
I never knew eggplant got so runny.
Next up, potato!
The skin's so crunchy.
It's like a potato chip!
I like the skin more than the inside.
Next, whole roasted avocado!
This one might be better raw...
Wait, weren't you making
something over there?
I think it could use a little more time.
I never knew you could warm
up packed meals this way.
Outdoor cooking seemed hard.
It might not be authentic, but...
That's not true.
I love having instant noodles when I camp.
Now, I'll let you have some of my favorite...
Fire-roasted sweet potato!
I think they turned out good.
It's so sweet!
All I did was wrap it in foil
and put it in the fire.
Did you use high-quality potatoes for this?
No.
Sweet Potatoes
100 yen per bag
They were on sale at the supermarket.
Huh...
I never knew it was so easy.
You could get started
just grilling meat, really.
Camp cooking is fun.
And even if you mess up and end up
with something weird, it's still fun.
The carrot turned black!
Y-You're right! I overcooked it!
It's so bitter!
It's charred to ash!
Yuck!
This might be okay...
I can't eat this! It's too bitter!
This is how grown-ups like it!
Haruka? Hiroto?
Dad!
You've been gone for a while. I got worried.
Oh... sorry.
You'll have to excuse my kids.
Oh, not at all.
I was the one who invited them.
Hey, try this.
It's a bit bitter...
Well, thank you for the food.
You're very welcome.
Bye, Onee-chan!
Bye.
Bye!
No signal
So she really was just out of range.
And she's already made friends.
Nadeshiko's amazing.
Dad, I think I'll cook something
the next time we come.
Even if it's something simple.
Sounds good.
Why don't we come with Mom next time?
Yeah!
I should have just camped at Amehata.
I'll have dinner on the way back...
Dad, are there deer or anything around here?
I'm not sure...
S-Sakura-san! You're here, too?
I'm sorry. Did I scare you?
Were you worried about Nadeshiko?
Well, I guess...
It was partly my fault for
suggesting things, so...
Thanks, Rin-chan.
What are you going to do now, Sakura-san?
I'm going home.
She seems all right on her own.
What about you?
I'm leaving, too.
This is Nadeshiko's solo camping trip.
Um...
Since we're here, why don't we visit the top?
I heard this place is
famous for its nightscape.
Sounds good.
Wow... This is a pretty amazing night view.
It is.
Lake Motosu, home of yummy curry noodles...
Ack! Nadeshiko!
It really is pretty!
All right.
What do you think she's doing?
Maybe her phone broke.
No signal
Nadeshiko
Is something wrong?
I'm out of range, but solo camping is fun!
Rin-chan, why don't we go into town?
I'll buy you dinner.
Okay.
I dream on...
Inu Inu Inuko-san
Inu Inu Inuko-san!
Caribou-kun is so cute.
You sure do like Caribou-kun, Aoi-chan.
I wish we had one at the Minobu branch.
I heard they sell plushies
at the Minobu Caribou.
No way.
It's got to be life-sized so you can hug it.
I heard you can buy the giant Caribou-kun.
What?! Really?!
We're at the campsite, Caribou-kun.
Indeed.
Indeed
The campfire's so pretty,
isn't it, Caribou-kun?
Indeed
Indeed.
Goodnight, Caribou-kun.
Indeed
Indeed.
Caribou-kun
What did I expect?
Next Episode
Winter's End and the Day of Departure
When camping...
Always mind the campsite
and facility rules. Don't forget to
take care of fires and your trash!
It gets cold during the winter.
Stay warm and be well-prepared!
Outdoor Activities Club